第七節，第43頁
Page 43, section 7.
我們需要解釋…
We'd like some clarification...
第七節對評估工具有所說明…
Section 7 has to do with  the evaluative measures by which...
「評估工具」
"Evaluative measures."
我們是在討論成績標準
What we're talking about here  are performance standards.
就這麼簡單
Plain and simple.
不行，會造成更多問題…
We can't have that.  We open that can of worms...
- 要拿掉，法蘭  - 總統府希望留著
-Gotta take it out, Frank.  -The Administration wants it in.
這是浪費時間
Then we're all wasting our time.
我能減少考試次數
Now, look, I can cut down  the frequency of testing,
- 但一定要是全面…  - 這會變得難以收拾
-but it's got to be a part of the overall...  -That's the thin edge of a 2-ton wedge.
- 沒得商量  - 等等
-No way. Non-debatable.  -All right, hold on.
聽他說說也不會怎麼樣
There's no harm in hearing him out, right?
法蘭，你的想法如何？
Frank, what do you have in mind?
我們調整第四條，給我第四條
We adjust article 4. Hand me article 4.
每三年一次，而不是每兩年…
We go every three years instead of two...
法蘭，要我們考慮考試…
Frank, for us to even consider testing...
馬帝，不能商量時間間隔
Marty, we can't negotiate time intervals here.
我只是說如果可以
If, I'm just saying if.
次數間隔不會超過五年
The frequency could never  be more than five years.
五年有點長，但如果你能改善…
Five is a little high.  But if you could bend on that...
- 馬帝  - 等等，不只是次數的問題
-Marty...  -Wait, wait, wait. And it's not just frequency.
資深教師會得到免稅
Veteran teachers would have to be exempt
如果他們有優秀教學的證明
if they have a proven record  of excellence with the students.
請等我一下
Well, excuse me for a moment.
克伊，你主持一下
Corey, will you take the reins on this?
是的，第四條關於免稅…
Right, so article 4, in terms of exemptions...
我已經說了多年  我們應該拆除
I've been saying for years  that we should tear it down.
青少年悲劇  郡長譴責議員
這是低俗，也是本郡的恥辱
It's vulgar.  It's an embarrassment to the county.
但法蘭安德沃屢次反對拆除
But time and time again, Frank Underwood  has fought to keep it standing.
要不是他  桃子水塔早就被取代了
If it weren't for him, the Peachoid  would've been replaced ages ago.
潔西卡馬斯特斯也會還在人間
And Jessica Masters would still be alive.
議員必須對這件悲劇做交代
The Congressman needs  to answer for this tragedy.
到底發生了什麼事？
What exactly happened?
17歲女孩衝出道路  傳簡訊給她男朋友，我引述
A 1 7-year-old girl ran off the road,  texting her boyfriend. And I quote,
「桃子水塔好像一個大…」  然後車就失控了
"Doesn't the Peachoid look like a giant..."  And then she lost control of the car.
老天
Jesus.
歐倫在地方媒體大做文章
Oren's making a big fuss in the local press.
他還慫恿父母控告蓋弗尼
And he's pushing the parents to sue Gaffney.
控告蓋弗尼？  這是他自己的管轄區
Sue Gaffney? It's in his own jurisdiction.
犧牲蓋弗尼再把你拖下水  挺值得的
It's worth throwing Gaffney under the bus  to drag you into the mess.
他又覬覦我的席位  他沒學到教訓嗎？
He's after my seat again.  Has he learned absolutely nothing?
這是不正當的競選
It's a full-on smear campaign, boss.
- 他會毀了你  - 用這個？
-He's out to destroy you.  -With this?
這只不過是個桃子  讓他自己出洋相
It's a peach for Christ's sake.  Let him make a fool out of himself.
不會，他會讓你出洋相
No, he will make a fool out of you.
如果他能讓全國媒體注意到
If he spins this right, gets national coverage.
全國媒體？這太誇張了
National coverage? It's a joke.
你就會很慘
And you will be the butt of it.
現在不能旁生枝節
We can't afford that right now.
你是教育提案的關注焦點
Not when you're in the spotlight  with the Education Bill.
這件事搞得我太多事
This thing has caused me  so much damn trouble.
- 我知道  - 所以該連絡誰？父母嗎？
-I know.  -So who should I call? Parents?
打電話不夠，你要親自拜訪
Phone call's not gonna cut it.  You need to go down there.
可以等到週一嗎？
Can it wait until Monday?
現在處理，就能控制局勢
We get on this thing right now,  we can contain it.
如果等到週一
We wait until Monday,
就無法預料  這個事件的渲染效應
and there's no way to know  how much this is gonna blow up on us.
我不能去蓋弗尼，工會才剛…
I can't go down to Gaffney.  The unions have just...
- 能延期  - 他們會很生氣的
-We postpone.  -They're gonna be livid.
馬帝很講道理  他會向他們解釋…
Marty's reasonable, okay?  He will explain to them...
他們就該理所當然接受
And they're just supposed  to understand and accept
我得離開協商桌
that I had to get up from the negotiating table
因為某個二流郡長想…
because some 2-bit  county administrator wants to...
我不想打斷你  但這不只是歐倫而已
I don't want to interrupt you, sir,  but this is not just about Oren.
還有父母
It's about the parents.
你想想這件訴訟
Now you think about the lawsuit.
要是你必須作證怎麼辦？
What happens ifyou have to testify?
傳票加上作證
Subpoenas. Depositions.
你扯進這件訴訟  教育提案就沒有前途了
You get dragged into a court battle,  there is no Education Bill.
我們不能忽視這件事
We can't ignore this.
我真的很恨這些小事
I just hate this small ball crap.
叫做什麼？
It's called the what?
- 桃子什麼？  - 桃子水塔
-The peach what?  -The Peachoid.
是一座桃子形狀的大水塔
It's a giant water tower  in the shape of a peach.
我剛上網查到了，桃子水塔…
Wow. I just googled it. The Peachoid...
她才17歲，琳達
She was 17, Linda.
你說得對，我很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
- 我需要多一周  - 不行
-I need another week.  -That's not gonna work.
總統將在週二演說  我們已經宣佈了
The President makes his speech on Tuesday.  We've already announced.
演說可以改期
Speeches can be rescheduled.
教育方面得有進展，法蘭
We have to show some progress  on Education, Frank.
百日就快到了
The first 100 days is almost over.
如果把演說延期  我們會像在原地打轉
We push back the speech,  it'll look like we're spinning our wheels.
好吧，我再想辦法  謝謝你，琳達
All right. I'll work something out.  Thank you, Linda.
法蘭，這是全國  兩大教育工會的會長
Frank, these are the heads of the two  largest teachers unions in the country.
我明白
I understand.
週末搭機過來
They flew here on a weekend.
道格會主持  菲利普議員很熟練…
Doug will lead the charge,  Congressman Phillips is well versed...
法蘭，他們是來和你見面  你負責這項提案
They flew here to see you, Frank.  You're managing this bill.
把這個放到另一個袋子裏  我會保持連絡
Put this in the other bag.  And I'll be in constant communication.
有大事，就打電話給我
Anything big comes up,  I'm a phone call away.
這是三百頁的文件  我們需要你坐鎮
It's a 300-page document.  We need you in that room.
我也很想留下  但這是我的戶籍區
I would stay if I could,  but this is my home district.
馬帝，幫個忙吧  我們會搞定這件事
Now, Marty, cut me a little slack here.  We'll get it done.
我們認識這麼久了  我何時讓你失望過？
You and I go way back.  Have I ever let you down?
- 從來沒有  - 我不想破例
-No, you haven't.  -And I don't intend to start now.
有人嗎？
Hello?
新水計劃
- 吉莉安？  - 克萊兒
-Gillian?  -Claire.
真高興終於見到你了
So nice to finally meet you.
我有一點不舒服  我不想害你生病
I'm a little under the weather,  I don't want to get you sick.
- 如果你不舒服，我們能…  - 沒關係，只是小感冒
-Well, if you're feeling ill, we can...  -No, no, no. I'm fine. It's just a cold.
- 謝謝你來  - 應該的
-Well, thank you for coming in.  -Of course.
到我的辦公室談好嗎？
Shall we talk in my office?
- 這些照片很酷  - 謝謝
-These are really cool photographs.  -Thank you.
亞當蓋羅威拍攝的  你有聽過他嗎？
Adam Galloway took the pictures.  Have you heard of him?
沒有
No.
幾年前我在惠特尼雙年展  認識他的
I met him at the Whitney Biennial  a couple years ago
我請他拍攝這些照片  他剛在現代美術館辦完展
and commissioned him to do these.  He just had a big show at PS1.
我對藝術不太瞭解
I'm not up to date on the art world.
沒關係，反正我們也不是  要討論藝術，對嗎？
That's all right, we're not here  to talk about photography, are we?
我辦公室在這邊
My office is over here.
- 有問題就找我  - 我能處理
-You run into any trouble, you call me.  -I got it covered.
- 吉克萊西知道我要來嗎？  - 剛跟他說過
-Gene Clancy know I'm coming?  -Just spoke to him.
廢話少說
Get to it.
班機訂好了，55分鐘後起飛  愛德會陪你去
Your flight is booked. Leaves in 55 minutes.  Ed will be joining you.
史提夫呢？
Where's Steve?
他一小時前請病假回家了，議員
He went home sick about an hour ago, sir.
- 我來代班  - 你叫什麼名字？
-I'll be filling in.  -What's your name again?
- 愛德華什麼？  - 米契
-Edward what?  -Meechum.
米契，你開車快嗎？
You drive fast, Meechum?
華府先驅報
- 你找我嗎？  - 喬伊，進來吧
-You wanted to talk to me?  -Come on in, Zoe.
這位是堤登太太，擁有…
This is Mrs. Tilden, owner of...
她知道我是誰
She knows who I am.
堤登太太很喜歡  你的凱薩琳杜倫報導
Mrs. Tilden liked your profile  on Catherine Durant.
我沒有
No, I didn't.
我愛死了
I loved it.
有深度又不讓步
In-depth. Uncompromising.
通常我不在出稿前看文章
Normally I don't read things  before they go to print,
但是凱西是我的朋友
but Cathy's a friend.
告訴我你如何事先知道  她會被提名？
Tell me how you knew  she'd be nominated before she did?
- 你要我的消息來源？  - 湯姆說你不告訴他
-You want my source?  -Tom says you won't tell him.
我沒告訴過任何人
I haven't told anyone.
我是報社老闆
Well, I own the paper.
我很慶幸能在這裏工作
And I'm very grateful to be working here.
你也不願意告訴我嗎？
So, you're not gonna tell me either?
你要什麼？  我的消息來源還是職業道德？
Which do you want,  my source or my integrity?
湯姆
Tom,
把喬伊的文章移到週日頭版
move Zoe's piece to the front page  of Sunday's edition.
讓我再想想
Let me think that over.
你好好地想  想完後把文章放到頭版
You think it over as much as you want.  Then put it on the front page.
我好不容易  才讓世安站穩腳步
I've worked really hard  to gain a foothold with WorldWell.
六年前只有我一個人  和一台電腦
Six years ago it was just me and a MacBook.
我明白
I understand.
我要兼兩份差才能付房租
And I had to juggle two temp jobs just  to pay the rent.
這是你的寶貝，你不想放手
It's your baby. You don't want to let it go.
我只是…
Well, I just...
你不用放手，吉莉安
And you wouldn't have to, Gillian.
我只要你繼續經營  你建立起來的事業
All I want is for you to grow  what you've already built.
聽說你解雇了一半的員工
I heard you fired halfyour staff.
對
Yes, I did.
這讓我很擔心
That worries me.
我開除他們  是要騰出空位給你
I let them go to make room for you.
我不確定我們適不適合
I'm just not sure we're the right match.
老實說，我有點不太習慣
To be honest, I'm a little uncomfortable  working with someone
跟請知名攝影師的人合作
who's commissioning famous photographers
因為我連幫義工買公車票  到辦公室的錢都沒有
when I can't even buy my volunteers  bus fare to the office.
知道妮奇韓慕樂是誰嗎？
Do you know who Nikki Hemler is?
不知道
No.
妮奇擁有卻爾西  最大的一間藝廊
Nikki owns one of the biggest galleries  in Chelsea.
她很想代表亞當蓋羅威
She desperately wanted  to represent Adam Galloway.
我把亞當介紹給她
I delivered on Adam,
回報是她每年  捐大約四萬元給淨水創權
and in return she contributes  almost 40 grand a year to CWl.
那筆錢能用在影響調查  遊說和研究
That money goes to impact studies,  lobbying efforts, research.
世安能從那種錢中受惠  吉莉安
WorldWell could benefit from  that sort of money, Gillian,
你的專業也能讓我們受惠
and we can benefit from your expertise.
我可以考慮嗎？
Can I think about it?
當然，不用急著決定
Of course.  We don't have to jump into anything.
我在這個鄉下地方長大
I grew up here, in the up-country.
聖經、烤肉，還有斷背山
Bibles, barbecues and broken backs.
南方什麼事都更混濁一點
Everything gets just a little bit thicker  this far south.
空氣、血液，甚至我
The air, the blood, even me.
我至少每個月下來一次
I try to make it down here  at least once a month.
蓋弗尼
每次回來都提醒著我  自己的努力成果
Every trip is a reminder of how far I've come.
我小時候什麼都沒有  我恨蓋弗尼
I hated Gaffney as a kid, when I had nothing.
但現在，我學會如何珍惜
But now, I've come to appreciate it.
不像以前那麼壓抑
It's not as suffocating as it once was,
除了要處理這種無稽之事
except when I have  to deal with the sort of nonsense
讓我很想上吊自殺
that makes me want to hang myself.
120號公路左轉
Turn left on Route 120.
- 別聽她說，我知道更近的路  - 是的，議員
-Don't listen to her. I know a better way.  -Yes, sir.
我們沒錢了，法蘭  光是法律費用就會壓垮我們
We don't have the money, Frank.  The legal bills alone will kill us.
若能達成協議呢？
How about a settlement?
我再看看數目
I'll look at the numbers.
- 你覺得看起來像什麼？  - 像個桃子
-What's it look like to you?  -Like a peach.
我是說到底看起來像什麼？
No, I mean, what does it really look like?
以市長的立場  我肯定覺得像個桃子
As mayor, I stick with a peach.
以一個市民的立場
As a private citizen,
看來像陽光照不到的地方
well it looks like the sun is shining  where it shouldn't be.
應該有更好的解決辦法
There's a better way to handle this.
法蘭，什麼辦法？
Really, Frank? And what's that?
我不想跟你吵架
I'm not trying to start an argument here.
你的口氣好像我是錯的
Now, you make it sound like  I'm in the wrong.
你心知肚明，歐倫
You know exactly what you're doing, Oren.
你利用這個可憐女孩的悲劇  鞏固自己的政壇優勢
You're using this poor girl's death  for your own political advantage.
是你對抗我
You're the one that fought me
桃農大發牢騷  抱怨我拆除的決定
when the Peach Farmers bitched  and moaned about me tearing it down.
你拿了他們的錢
You're the one who took their money.
- 只不過是水塔  - 很不道德
-It's a water tower.  -It's ungodly.
- 歐倫…  - 這是老套，法蘭
-Oren...  -This is cut and dry, Frank.
我想盡辦法要拆除  你則想盡辦法和我做對
I fought to tear it down,  you fought to keep it up.
那個女孩的車禍是你的錯  我卻替你背黑鍋
That girl's blood is on your hands.  And I'm taking you to task for it.
這樣說好了  迪克彼得斯這任期完會退休
All right, I tell you what,  Dick Peters is gonna retire this term.
這表示第四區  會有一場公開競選
That means there's an open race  in the 4th district.
要是我幫你贏得席位呢？
How about I help you lock up that seat?
我不想跟你做協議，法蘭
I'm not looking to make a deal, Frank.
這不是協議，這是一個機會
It's not a deal, it's an opportunity.
我不用你幫忙
I'll be just fine.
歐倫，你可以鄙視我
You may despise me, Oren,
但上道的話應該  請我們上去喝杯冰茶
but the classy thing to do would've been  to invite us up for some of that iced tea.
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
你不該在這裏慢跑
You shouldn't run here.
很可恥
It's disgraceful.
你不懂得尊重嗎？
Have you no respect?
這標準只是起點  是建議，不是強制規定
The criteria is a starting point.  They're suggested, not mandated.
我們召集專家委員會  他們將會決定…
We assemble a council of experts  who will determine exactly...
上面沒寫這些專家的身份  或是遴選方式
Nowhere here does it say who these  experts are or how they'll be chosen.
總統遴選委員會
The President selects the council.
- 有什麼監督？  - 請提供遴選意見
-With what sort of oversight?  -We'd like input on the selection.
- 道格，跟琳達確定一下  - 打給她了
-Doug, check with Linda.  -Calling her now.
好的，現在可以討論一下  特許學校嗎？
Okay, so, now,  can we talk about charter schools?
- 特許學校絕對不行  - 一定要有
-Charter schools are a no-go.  -They have to be in there.
- 你要保留，我們走人  - 我們也一樣
-You keep them in, we walk.  -The same goes for us.
請不要馬上下最後通牒
Let's notjump to ultimatums.
那我們就想辦法  減少非公立學校的費用
Well, then let's figure out a way  to reduce non-public spending.
好吧，給我幾分鐘想想
All right.  Give me a few minutes to think about that.
一定要解決這一點  才能繼續下去
We can't move forward  without addressing this point.
我明白，但這是提案的基石
I understand, but this is the cornerstone  of the bill.
我們談一談吧
Let's talk it out.
好的，給我五分鐘，馬帝  我會馬上回電
All right, give me five minutes, Marty.  I'll call you right back.
不行…
No, no...
如果我們考慮協議  就要有能力付他們錢
If we consider settling as an option,  we need to be able to pay them.
但是如果我們提出協議  不就表示我們…
But if we offer a settlement,  aren't we saying...
我就是這個意思  我們承認城鎮害死這個女孩
That's my point, we're admitting that  the town's responsible for this kid's death.
我想讓桃農擔這個責任
I say make the Peach Farmers cough it up.
看看這筆爛帳
Oh, man, talk about a shitstorm.
討論到哪裏了？
Y'all mind catching me up?
維恩和崔維斯想出庭
Wayne and Travis want to go to court.
我覺得不適當
I don't think that's a good idea.
我們不能花錢買協議  市政費用都快入不敷出
We can't be pouring money into a settlement  when we can barely afford to run the city.
傑米，你覺得如何？
What do you think, Jamie?
我們要擔心桃農協會
I think that we gotta worry about  the Peach Farmers Association.
如果我們有譴責  桃子水塔的跡象
If there is a hint that  we're blaming the Peachoid,
- 他們一定不會妥協…  - 誰理他們？
-they're gonna raise holy hell...  -Who gives a crap?
- 他們得接受  - 讓他說
-They gotta suck it up.  -Let him talk.
我只是說我們要把他們考慮進去
I'm just saying that we need  to keep them in mind.
追根究底，她犯了法  你不能邊開車邊傳簡訊
She was breaking the law. End of story.  You can't text while you drive.
但是陪審團只會看到
Yeah, but all the jury is gonna see
一個美麗的17歲女孩死了
is a beautiful 17-year-old girl  who's now dead.
對不起，法蘭，你才剛來
No offense, Frank, but you just got here.
我們從上周  就開始處理這件事了
We've been dealing with this  for the last week now.
解決方案是什麼？
And where's your solution?
你覺得你比我們厲害嗎？
What, you think you know better than us?
我只是想面對現實
I'm just trying to be realistic.
法蘭，我知道  你想要一舉解決難題
Frank, I know you want to swoop down  and save the day.
但這是原則問題
But there's a principle at stake here.
我們為了這個女孩  寧願被勒索…
We allow ourselves to be extorted  because of this teenager...
當歐倫讓陪審團  為這個死去的女孩痛哭流涕
When Oren gets a jury to weep a river  of snot over this dead girl,
當蓋弗尼經濟不景氣
when Gaffney goes tits up
因為你付不起七位數的遮口費
because you can't afford  to pay a seven-figure award in damages,
當你們都被趕下台  我也輸給契斯
when you all get booted out of office,  and I lose to Chase,
你們再來跟我說原則的事
then you can chew my ear off  about principles,
因為我們時間多得很
because we'll all have nothing but time  on our hands.
在此之前  你沒貢獻就閉嘴，崔維斯
Until then, you either contribute  or you keep it shut, Travis.
我們要這樣做
Now here's what we're gonna do.
吉，如果真要協議  我們能籌到多少？
Gene, how much could we pull together  for a settlement if we had to?
- 大概150  - 那應該夠
-About 150.  -That'll work.
傑米，叫你的兄弟們到五金行
Jamie, get your boys down  at the hardware store
做兩個告示牌  架在水塔兩邊一公里外
to build two billboards, put them out  a mile out on either side of the tower.
寫說「小心駕駛  請勿邊開車邊傳簡訊」
Have 'em read, "Drive safely.  No texting behind the wheel."
- 知道了  - 在明天前做好
-Got it.  -And get those up by tomorrow morning.
我會發許可證
I'll issue the permits.
晚上別再用燈照那玩意了
And let's stop lighting the thing at night.
桃農不會喜歡這個舉動
The Peach Farmers aren't gonna like that.
電費要多少？
How much does the electric cost?
一個月四千一百多  一年大概五萬
$4,100 plus change per month.  About $50,000 a year.
老天，這費用足夠  一個孩子念完大學了…
Jesus, you could put a kid  through college on it...
用這筆錢以她的名義  創辦一個獎學金
Let's use that money to start  a scholarship fund in her name.
你跟協會的人說  他們要點燈，就要付電費
Meantime, you tell the Association  if they want it lit up, they can pay for it.
我會開心地傳消息
I'll deliver that message happily.
幫我擬一份  可以除掉括約肌的預算
And do me up a budget  and a plan for removing the sphincter.
什麼？
The what?
他是指緊急閥
He means the emergency valve.
真有趣  我一直以為那是陰蒂
That's interesting,  I've always thought of it as a clitoris.
但那在底部  我相信陰蒂是在上面…
But it's on bottom.  I believe the clitoris is above the...
- 但如果你想像女人趴著…  - 夠了
-But if you imagine a woman on her belly...  -Enough.
做好這件事
I want it done.
還有，吉  給我所有道路規則的法規
And, Gene, get me everything  you've got on road regulations.
郡法，不是市法
County statutes, not municipal.
你還記得上次選舉  搞的那個電線事件嗎？
And you remember that power line business  we pulled up at the last election?
當然
Sure do.
一定要堅若盤石
Let's make sure we're rock solid on that.
這頓昂貴的晚餐
Does this very expensive dinner
至少能買到  一晚令人難忘的性愛？
at least buy me an evening  of mind-blowing sexual congress?
是很好，但沒有那麼好…
It was good,  but I don't know if it was that good...
口交可以嗎？
Fellatio good?
也許打手槍吧，不保證
A hand job, maybe. No promises.
成交
Deal.
彼得，我有件事必須跟你說
Hey, Peter, there's something  I need to tell you.
我最近在想
I have been thinking lately,
也許在別的地方工作會好一點
you know, it might be good  to work somewhere else.
我去了幾次面試
So I did some interviews.
發言人辦公室  請我擔任立法主任代理人
And the Speaker's office  offered me Deputy L.D.
彼得？
Peter?
克裏絲汀娜…
Christina...
我只是想說  對我們的未來會有幫助
I just thought it could be good, right,  if we're going to have any future.
停止這種主管員工的關係  當真正的情侶…
To stop this boss-staffer thing.  Be a real couple...
我們是情侶
We are a real couple.
我是說不用在辦公室裏  偷偷摸摸
I mean, not have to hide it,  like we do at the office.
幫發言人工作是很好的機會
And it's a great opportunity. The Speaker.
如果我接受這個工作  你會恨我嗎？
Would you hate me if I took the job?
寶貝，我希望你得到你想要的
Baby, I want what you want.
我不會反對  只要你覺得這是你該做的
I won't fight you on this.  Not if this is what you feel you need to do.
- 真的？  - 對
-Really?  -Yeah.
你沒錯，這是很好的機會
And you're right. This is a great opportunity.
何時要答覆他們？
When do you have to tell them by?
沒有期限，我不用馬上決定
There's no deadline.  I don't have to decide right away.
那你決定以後  幫我找個替代你的人
Okay. Well, when you do decide,  just, you know, help me find a replacement.
- 讓我知道一下  - 那當然
-You know, give me a heads up.  -Yeah, of course.
我還沒決定是否要接受
I haven't even decided if I'm going to take it.
我們不用現在講清楚  我只是想提一下
We don't have to talk this through right now.  I just thought I'd bring it up.
- 我們該走了吧？  - 是的
-Should we get out of here?  -Yes.
去找父母吧
Let's go find the parents.
- 你在車上等  - 人很多，先生
-You hang back by the car.  -It's a big crowd, sir.
如果我在安慰兩位悲傷父母時  被槍殺或刺死
If I get shot or stabbed  consoling two grieving parents,
我會是永遠的英雄
I'm a hero from now until the end of time.
來賭一把吧？
Let's roll the die, shall we?
議員，我不能允許你  獨自進入那群人裏
Sir, I can't allow you  to go unescorted into all those people.
允許我？
Allow me?
米契，有件事你要搞清楚
Let's get one thing straight, Meechum.
你無法命令我做任何事
You are never to dictate  what I can and cannot do.
當我要你做事  我只要聽到你說
The only two words I want to hear from you  when I ask you to do something
是的，議員
are "yes" and "sir."
- 明白了嗎？  - 是的，議員
-ls that understood?  -Yes, sir.
很好，我們應該合得來
Good. Then we're gonna get along just fine.
馬斯特斯夫婦  我是議員法蘭安德沃
Mr. and Mrs. Masters,  I'm Frank Underwood, your Congressman.
請節哀順變
I'm so sorry for your loss.
- 我無法體會…  - 沒錯，你不能
-I cannot begin to fathom...  -You're right, you can't.
你完全不懂
You have no idea.
- 原諒我，我無意打擾，我…  - 你已經打擾了
-Forgive me. I don't mean to intrude. I just...  -Well, you are intruding.
狄恩，請求你…
Dean, please...
這不是他的錯嗎？
What? It's his fault, isn't it?
我只是想來表達我的慰問
Anyway, I just wanted  to express my condolences
如果你們有任何需要…
and say if there's anything the two of you...
狄恩，你不用跟他說話  我們已經採取法律行動
Dean, you don't want to be talking to him.  We got legal action pending.
我知道契斯先生  跟你們說了什麼，相信…
Look, I know what Mr. Chase  has been saying, and believe...
沒有人邀請你
Nobody invited you.
沒有人要聽你的慰問或是辯解
Nobody wants your condolences,  or your excuses.
法蘭，拜託你
Frank, please.
現在你不該忍受這種事
You shouldn't have  to put up with this right now.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
還算順利吧
Well, that went well.
牧師，等一下！
Hang on a second. Reverend!
議員
Congressman.
很高興再見到你  目前情況不是很適合
Nice to see you again.  I wish it was under better circumstances.
- 很糟糕，對嗎？  - 真糟糕
-Terrible, isn't it?  -It's just terrible.
你安排得很周到
This is so thoughtful,  what you've organized here.
只是盡點微薄之力
Least we can do.
馬斯特斯家是你的教友嗎？
Tell me, are the Masters  in your congregation?
是的，他們每週日都來
They are. They come every Sunday.
他們明天會去做禮拜嗎？
You think they'll be at the service tomorrow?
應該會的
I'd be surprised if they weren't.
能否請你幫我一個忙？
I'm wondering, can you do me a favor?
什麼事都行，法蘭
Anything for you, Frank.
- 藍色牙刷是你的，對嗎？  - 對，藍色的
-The blue toothbrush is yours, right?  -Yeah, the blue one.
- 彼得？  - 什麼事？
-Hey, Peter?  -Yeah?
你把燈泡收到哪裏了？  臥房的檯燈壞了
Where do you keep the light bulbs?  The lamp in the bedroom is out.
在廚房水槽的下面
In the kitchen, under the sink.
這是我的想法
Here's what I think,
我希望能更有氣度  但我做不到
and I wish I could be bigger than this,  but I can't.
我自私，只想到自己
And I'm being selfish,  and I realize it's mostly about me,
但算了
but fuck it.
我必須說
I have to say it.
請不要接受那個工作  克裏絲汀娜
Please don't take that other job, Christina.
這是我的感受
Anyway, that's how I feel.
很高興你告訴我
I'm glad you told me.
特許學校會危及  我們的組織能力，很合理
Charters jeopardize our ability to organize,  which is reason enough.
最大的問題  是比較他們的成功…
But the bigger issue  is that measuring their success against...
特許學校的評估標準  應該也要一樣…
Charter schools would operate under  the same evaluative standards that every...
根本是雞同鴨講  無論你怎麼看
Apples and oranges,  no matter how you look at it.
你不能用同樣的標準來比較
You can't use the same standards  to compare.
你是說特許學校的標準  要比其他學校
What, you're advocating  a more demanding criteria
更嚴格？
for charter schools than other schools?
很簡單，法蘭
Our point is simple, Frank.
聯邦補助應該只給公立學校
Federal funds should only go  to public union school districts.
等一下
Hold on a sec.
但我們已經增加  非特許學校的補助一成
Yeah, but we've already increased  non-charter funding by 10%.
給特許學校的補助微不足道
The amount going  to charter schools is negligible.
法蘭，重點是慣例  不是數字
It's the precedent, Frank, not the number.
我們建立很多慣例，馬帝  這是改革的本質
We're setting a lot of precedents, Marty.  That's the nature of reform.
有些可以接受，有些不行
Well, some of them we can stomach,  some of them we can't.
別偏離主題，不切實際  來談談細節
All right, let's not get bogged down  in abstractions, let's deal with specifics.
克伊，請你解釋一下
Corey, can you walk us through it?
有個三階段方案
There is a three-prong approach
來決定補助額…
to determining the amount of funding  a particular...
想我嗎？
Miss me?
可能有一點
Maybe a little.
有多久了，15個小時？
What's it been, 15 hours?
還不夠久到發現你不在了
Not even long enough to notice you're gone.
跟馬帝史皮奈拉說
Tell that to Marty Spinella.
- 進行得如何？  - 在進行
-How's it coming?  -It's coming.
又慢又難受
Slowly. Painfully.
前院一直都有鬱金香
Hey, have we always had  tulips in the front yard,
還是我慢慢失去理智了？
or am I slowly going insane?
我在去年秋天種的
I planted them. Last fall.
你沒有吧
You did not.
在我跟你一起競選的時候
When I was down with you for the campaign.
你從來沒有種過花
You've never gardened a day in your life.
胡說，我有種過一天花
Not true.  I have gardened exactly one day in my life.
你在史巴登堡做募款活動
You were down in Spartanburg  doing some sort of fundraiser.
吉的老婆帶來一桶球莖
Gene's wife came over  with a bucket of bulbs.
一轉眼，我就跪在土裏
And next thing you know  I was down on my knees in the dirt,
連蚯蚓都來了
earthworms and all.
我完全不能想像
I can't even picture it.
我也不能，但是我做的
Neither can l, and I was there.
還有什麼？
What else?
讓我暫時拋開大桃子  跟死去的少女
Distract me from giant peaches  and dead teenagers.
還有呢…
What else...
今天我去跑步  發生了一件怪事…
I went for a run today, and the strangest...
這個女人…
I don't know, this woman...
- 那很有趣  - 什麼很有趣？
-That's interesting.  -What is?
68小時，23分鐘，11秒
喬伊邦斯剛傳來簡訊
Text just came. Zoe Barnes.
誰？
Who?
你那天見過的《先軀報》記者
That reporter from The Herald  you met one night.
我記得她  去吧，如果你要打回去給她
Her. I remember.  Yeah, go, if you need to call her back.
沒關係，她可以等  我在跟我太太說話
No, she can wait. I'm talking to my wife.
沒關係，我反正要去睡覺了  明天見？
That's okay. I'm going to bed soon anyway.  See you tomorrow?
希望如此，祝我好運
I hope so. Wish me luck.
晚安，我的小桃子水塔
Bonsoir, ma petite Peachoid.
噁心
Disgusting.
- 晚安  - 晚安
-Good night.  -Good night.
好的，那樣可以，克伊  馬帝？
Yeah, all right, that's fine, Corey. Marty?
法蘭，還有一點解釋要做  問題在這裏
Frank, had a little bit of explaining to do.  Here's our problem.
解釋？
上次說完之後…
你在哪裏？
你在做什麼？
下個消息是什麼？
提供給我
南卡羅來納州  地區的事
說話方便嗎？
現在不行，有事在忙
還有什麼比我更迫切？
沒有人可以阻擋你
無法阻擋…  你還沒看我開始呢
我沒辦法想像
我賭你可以
我賭你看過
明天看《起點》  我會給你一個飛吻
法蘭？你在嗎？
Frank? Frank, did we lose you?
是的，我在這裏，馬帝
Yeah, I'm here, Marty.
我們可以兜圈子討論  特許學校的事
Look, we can talk ourselves in circles  about charter schools,
但我提議…
but here's what I propose...
你在文章裏詳細提到
In your profile you go into great detail
喬伊邦斯採訪
杜倫在早期職業生涯中  遇到性別歧視
about the sexism Durant faced  early on in her career.
是的，她首次當選時  參議院還是男人的天下
That's right. When she was first elected,  it was still an old boys' club in the Senate.
不久前新聞業也是如此
Journalism used to be that way too  not so long ago.
我覺得很幸運
I feel really lucky.
在我之前有很多先軀
I've had lots of trailblazers come before me.
比如說，我的同事  珍妮史柯斯基
For instance, my colleague, Janine Skorsky,
她是《先軀報》首位女性  成為主要政治記者
was the first woman at The Herald  to become chief political correspondent.
那才是五年前的事
And that was only five years ago.
這些先軀  讓你能發展得這麼快嗎？
Has it been those trailblazers  who've allowed you to rise so quickly?
你從都會版晉陞到週日頭版
You've moved up from the metro pages  to the front page Sunday edition.
如果珍妮沒有鋪好路
Well, I don't know that  that would be possible
我應該沒有可能
if Janine hadn't already paved the way.
這是否表示  《先軀報》還是很傳統？
So does that mean that The Herald  is not particularly progressive?
他們很先進
I think that they are.
湯姆心胸寬大
Tom is very open-minded.
是他讓珍妮陞官的
He's the reason Janine got promoted.
那是主編湯姆翰默史密
That's Tom Hammerschmidt,  the executive editor.
- 對，我們都叫他「錘子」  - 「錘子」？為什麼？
-Yes, we actually call him "The Hammer. "  -"The Hammer"? Why?
因為他很強硬
Because he's tough.
如何強硬？
How tough?
湯姆的要求很高
Tom has very high standards.
我很愛他
I love him.
他是個很棒的良師益友
He's a great mentor.
有時候很令人抓狂
It can be frustrating at times.
他會要你一而再再而三檢查
He makes you double  and triple-check things.
你一拿到新聞就想發表
And you want to get the news out  the moment you have it,
但他會要你重寫到完美  這就是《先軀報》的精神
and he makes you rewrite until it's perfect,  but that's what makes The Herald The Herald.
在網路時代  這是可行的模式嗎？
Is that a workable model in the Internet age?
我們的讀者認為如此
Our readers think it is.
你們的讀者人數在下降
You have a declining readership.
但我不覺得是湯姆的責任  那是時勢所趨吧？
But I don't lay that at Tom's feet.  I think that that's the times we live in, right?
報社應該順應潮流嗎？
Should newspapers adapt  to the times we live in?
《先軀報》不是不願做調整
It's not that The Herald refuses to adapt.
我們有網路版
We have an online presence.
也許調整得不夠快？
Is that maybe not adapting fast enough?
我不會否認
I wouldn't argue with that statement.
我們能做得更多
We could do more.
今天我們有個特別的客人
We've got a special guest with us today.
他希望今早能有機會  和我們分享幾句話
He asked for the opportunity to share  a few words with us this morning.
我們的議員，法蘭安德沃
Our very own Congressman,  Frank Underwood.
- 早安  - 早安
-Good morning.  -Good morning.
謝謝你，牧師  還要謝謝唱詩班美麗的歌聲
Thank you, Reverend. And thanks  to the choir for that beautiful hymn.
今早我想念一段…
I want to read this morning from...
不是
No.
你知道大家最不想  討論的話題是什麼嗎？
You know what no one wants to talk about?
仇恨
Hate.
我很瞭解仇恨
I know all about hate.
是從你的心底開始
It starts in your gut. Deep down here.
在那裏蠢蠢欲動，不斷累積
Where it stirs and churns. And then it rises.
仇恨會快速累積又猛烈
Hate rises, fast and volcanic.
然後爆發，烈焰沖天
It erupts, hot on the breath.
你的眼睛充滿怒火
Your eyes go wide with fire.
你咬緊牙關  你覺得牙齒會崩裂
You clench your teeth so hard  you think they'll shatter.
我恨你，老天
I hate you, God.
我恨你！
I hate you!
別告訴我你沒說過那樣的話  我知道你有
Don't tell me you haven't said  those words before. I know you have.
我們都說過
We all have.
如果你曾痛徹心扉
If you've ever felt soul-crushing loss.
今天在座有兩位父母  明白那樣的悲痛
There are two parents with us today  who know that pain.
天下父母最深的痛  就是白髮人送黑髮人
The most terrible hurt of all,  losing a child before her time.
如果狄恩和莉安現在站起來
If Dean and Leanne were  to stand up right now
大聲喊出仇恨的言語  我們能責備他們嗎？
and scream those awful words of hate,  could we blame them?
我不會
I couldn't.
至少我能體會他們的仇恨  我能瞭解
At least their hatred I can understand.  I can grasp it.
但是上帝的放縱和殘酷
But God's wantonness, his cruelty,
我無法開始…
I can't even begin to...
我的父親在43歲的時候  死於心臟病
My father dropped dead of a heart attack  at the age of 43, 43 years old.
他過世時  我向上帝說了這些話
And when he died, I looked up to God  and I said those words.
因為我的父親還那麼年輕  充滿朝氣和夢想
Because my father was so young,  so full of life, so full of dreams.
為什麼上帝要把他帶走？
Why would God take him from us?
其實我根本不瞭解他  也不知道他的夢想是什麼
Truth be told I never really knew him,  or what his dreams were.
他很安靜、膽小  幾乎沒有人注意到他
He was quiet, timid, almost invisible.
我的母親看不起他  我的外婆恨他
My mother didn't think much of him.  My mother's mother hated him.
一個從沒做過大事的人
The man never scratched the surface of life.
也許他那麼早過世是好事  他的存在沒有意義
Maybe it's best he died so young,  he wasn't doing much but taking up space.
但是這種悼詞  不太有感染力吧？
But that doesn't make for  a very powerful eulogy, now does it?
我擦乾眼淚大喊  「為什麼，上帝？
I wept. I screamed, "Why, God?
「我怎麼能不恨你奪走
"How can I not hate you  when you steal from me
「這世上我最愛也最崇拜的人？
"the person I most love  and admire in this world?
「我不明白，所以我恨你」
"l don't understand it, and I hate you for it."
舊約聖經箴言中說
The Bible says in Proverbs,
「全心相信上帝
"Trust in the Lord with all your heart
「不要依靠自己的判斷力
"and lean not on your own understanding.
「不要依靠自己的判斷力」
"Lean not on your own understanding."
上帝要我們相信他
God is telling us to trust him.
就算我們無知還是要愛他
To love him despite our own ignorance.
若我們無法忍受  最艱難的考驗就不算信仰了
After all, what is faith if it doesn't endure  when we are tested the most?
我們永遠不會明白  為什麼上帝要帶走潔西卡
We will never understand  why God took Jessica,
或是我的父親或任何人
or my father or anyone.
上帝無法給我們答案時  他給了我們愛的能力
And while God may not give us any answers,  he has given us the capacity for love.
我們的責任是愛他  而不是質問他的計劃
Our job is to love him  without questioning his plan.
所以我向禰禱告，親愛的神
So I pray to you, dear Lord.
請求禰給我們力量  繼續愛禰
I pray to you to help strengthen  our love for you,
用禰溫暖的愛  來擁抱狄恩和莉安
and to embrace Dean and Leanne  with the warmth of your love in return.
我向禰禱告  希望禰能幫我們擊退仇恨
And I pray that you will help us  fend off hatred,
我們能真心全意相信禰
so that we may all truly trust  in you with all our hearts,
不要依靠自己的判斷力
and lean not on our own understanding.
阿門
Amen.
你的工作是報導新聞  不是製造新聞
Your job is to the report the news,  not be the news.
- 我在宣傳報社  - 你是在宣傳喬伊邦斯
-I was promoting the paper.  -You were promoting Zoe Barnes.
這是因為我說  我們叫你「錘子」嗎？
Is this about how I said  we called you "The Hammer"?
- 如果你不高興，我道歉  - 你沒搞清楚狀況
-Because if that upset you, I apologize.  -You're missing the point.
我不希望你跟別人說  我們這裏的事
I don't want you talking about  anything that happens here.
不要說綽號、我們有多先進  或是我們採用網路
Not nicknames, not how progressive we are,  not whether we're adapting to the lnternet.
你對這家報社的任何意見  都不要說出去
Any thoughts you have about this paper  you keep them to yourself
你可以來跟我說
or you bring them to me.
你不該上電視開始…
You don't get on national television  and start...
抱歉，我不想…
I'm sorry, I wasn't trying to...
不要插嘴
Don't interrupt when I'm talking.
你能像大人一樣跟我說話  湯姆
You can speak to me like an adult, Tom.
不用像在跟小女孩說教一樣
You don't have to lecture me like a little girl.
你還沒有到大人的地步
You haven't earned the right  to be treated as an adult.
你以為幾篇頭版新聞  還有電視專訪
You think a few front page stories  and some face time on TV
就能讓你成為  下一個朱蒂米勒？
makes you the next Judy Miller?
你還有很長一段路要走  不要太囂張
You've got a long way to go.  Don't be so arrogant.
你覺得女人要求你尊敬她  表示她很囂張？
Okay, so you think when a woman asks  to be treated with respect, that's arrogance?
你是說我有性別歧視？
Are you accusing me of sexism?
只不過是聊天而已
Just making an observation.
不准上電視一個月
No TV for a month.
- 什麼？  - 你聽到了，不准接專訪
-What?  -You heard me. No interviews.
- 這真的很不公平  - 你要永遠都不能上電視嗎？
-That's completely unfair.  -You want to make it no TV indefinitely?
沒事了，你可以走了
We're done. You can go now.
喂？
Hello?
吉莉安，我是克萊兒安德沃  我能上來嗎？
Gillian, it's Claire Underwood.  Can I come up?
你有看醫生嗎？
Have you seen a doctor?
腸胃炎沒那麼嚴重  大概再一周就沒事了
Giardia's not so bad.  It'll pass in another week or so.
- 你沒有健保嗎？  - 沒有
-You don't have health insurance, do you?  -Nope.
我會幫你預約我的私人醫生  明天幫你看看
I'll make an appointment for you  to see my personal GP tomorrow.
吃藥沒什麼用  讓病自然過了就好了
Medicine doesn't really do much.  You have to let it run its course.
我們會在適當的監督下  讓病自然好
Well, we'll let it run its course  under proper supervision.
- 不要再拒絕了  - 克萊兒…
-I won't take no for an answer on this.  -Claire...
如果有必要  我會親自把你拖到醫院
I'll drag you to the hospital myself  if I have to.
你要看醫生，不要再跟我吵了
You're going to the doctor. No argument.
謝謝
Thanks.
他們要走了  完全聽不進我說的話
They're about to walk.  They won't listen to a word I say.
- 兩個工會都一樣？  - 對
-Both unions?  -Yeah.
叫馬帝聽電話
Put Marty on the phone.
等一下，馬帝
Hang on. Marty.
好，法蘭嗎？
Yeah. It's Frank?
這招沒用，法蘭
This isn't working, Frank.
馬帝，你必須把他們留在裏面
Marty, you have got  to keep them in that room.
他們失去耐性了  他們很不高興你不在，法蘭
They lost their patience, all right?  They're upset you're not in the room, Frank.
- 我今天下午會回來  - 太遲了
-I'll be back this afternoon.  -No. It's too late.
跟他們說我會過來  說明特許學校補助的事
Look, tell them I'll come down  on subsidies for charter schools.
就算如此  他們還是不喜歡成績標準
Even so, they're angry  about the performance standards.
這件事八字還沒一撇  還有很多要做…
We're not even halfway through this thing.  There's so much in it that they...
那跟他們說我能調整成績標準  每五年一次
Then tell them that I'll roll over on  performance standards. Five-year intervals.
你應該親自說，法蘭
It should be you telling them that, Frank.
在這個會議室
You, here at this table.
我知道，我盡力而為，馬帝
I know that.  You know, I'm doing the best I can, Marty.
但是我分身乏術
But I can't be in two places at once.
聽著，我向你保證  如果你能讓他們待在裏面
Now look, I promise you,  if you keep them in that room,
我回去後會很快解決這件事
we will get through this hump  as soon as I get back.
馬帝，你是他們的陳情代表  你知道什麼對他們最好
Marty, you are their lobbyist.  You know what's best for them.
幫幫他們吧
Save them from themselves.
好吧，我盡量試試
Okay. I'll see what I could do.
我是史坦普
It's Stamper.
不要讓史皮奈拉離開你的視線
Do not let Spinella out of your sight.
必要時把門鎖起來
And lock the goddamn doors if you have to.
瞭解
You got it.
好了
Here we go.
我知道你是大忙人  希望沒有耽擱你…
I know you're a busy man,  I hope we're not keeping you...
沒有，我時間多得很
No, no, no. I've got all the time in the world.
這是火腿，這些是火雞  還有馬鈴薯沙拉
This is ham and these are turkey.  And there's some potato salad.
禱告好嗎？
Shall we have a prayer?
親愛的上帝…
Gracious loving God...
- 你得過這種病嗎？  - 第三次了
-Have you had this before?  -This is the third time.
我已經習慣了
I'm used to it by now.
我不是很習慣  但是比瘧疾厲害
Well, I'm not used to it, but it beats malaria.
你得過瘧疾？
You've had malaria?
在辛巴威的時候病了一個月
In Zimbabwe. That took me out for a month.
你犧牲很大
You make a lot of sacrifices.
我不覺得是犧牲
I don't see it as a sacrifice.
你為了創辦非營利機構  拒絕谷歌六位數薪水的工作
You turned down a six-figure salary  at Google to start your own non-profit.
在帕羅奧多市不會有瘧疾
People don't get malaria in Palo Alto.
你有做功課
You do your research.
如果是我關心的人
When it's someone I care about.
克萊兒，我拒絕那份工作  因為我不想恨自己
Claire, I turned down that job  because I would've hated myself.
薪水很好，但是又如何？
It was a lot of money, but for what?
他們就能滿足  人種多樣性的配額
So they could fill their diversity quota
一個有史丹佛學歷的亞洲女生？
with an Asian girl  peddling a Stanford degree?
不是隨便的亞洲女生  是學生代表
Not just any Asian girl. A valedictorian.
讓我給你谷歌不能給你的東西
Let me offer you what Google couldn't.
我明白集能力  美麗和野心於一身的滋味
I know what it is to be capable  and beautiful and ambitious,
還有像謝吉和賴瑞擁有
and be on people like Sergey  and Larry's checklist
那些很有面子的戰利品
of things that look good to have on a shelf.
我不是在招攬你
I'm not trying to acquisition you.
你是一位讓我佩服的女性  這很難得
What I see in you is a woman I admire,  which doesn't happen often.
我希望能幫你  我想幫你排除萬難
I want to enable you.  I want to clear the way for you.
好讓你能達到  你想要完成的目標
So that you can achieve what you want  to achieve, on your own terms.
謝謝你請我喝茶
Thanks for the tea.
我明天會派車去接你看醫生
And I will send a car to pick you up  for the doctor tomorrow.
等你好了
When you're back on your feet,
你覺得我們可能繼續嗎？
do you think maybe  we can work something out?
是的，我覺得可以
Yes, I think we could.
這是她在高三時的舞會
That's her at junior prom.
好漂亮
Beautiful.
這是她穿皮夾克的時候
Here she is in her letter-jacket.
她高一就進了校隊
She made varsity as a freshman.
我記得她得知消息的那天
I remember the day she found out.
教練打電話來  潔西興奮的不得了
Coach called,  and Jessie starts jumping up and down,
「媽，你知道嗎？」
"Mom, guess what?"
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
別道歉，沒關係
Don't be. It's fine.
為什麼要這樣？
Why are we doing this?
老實說  舊事重提有什麼意義？
Honestly. What's to be gained  dredging up all this stuff?
有時回憶好事會有幫助
Remembering the good things  helps sometimes.
讓我的太太流淚時沒有幫助
Not when it puts my wife in tears.
我很感謝你在教堂裏說的話  但是對我們沒有用
I appreciate what you said at the church,  but it doesn't do us any good.
這也沒有用
Neither does this.
那我能幫到什麼？
Well, what can I do to help?
什麼都不行
You can't do anything.
她不在了
She's gone.
沒錯，我不能改變事實
You're right. I can't change that.
但是我可以保證市政府  賠償你們一大筆錢
But I can make sure the city offers you  a sizable settlement.
你是說收買我們？
You mean buy us off?
不是，我是說能幫你們  避免多年的官司
No, I mean help you avoiding  years of court battles.
潔西卡本來要上弗曼大學  對嗎？
Jessica was gonna go to Furman,  is that right?
- 排球獎學金？  - 對，全額獎學金
-On a volleyball scholarship?  -Yes, a full ride.
我今早跟大學校長談過了
Well, I spoke to the president  of the university this morning,
我們想以你女兒的名義  創辦一個新獎學金
and we'd like to create a new scholarship  in your daughter's name.
如果你們同意的話  由你們決定
If you'd like that. It's entirely up to you.
但最重要的是我們必須保證  這樣的事不會再發生
But most importantly we have to make sure  that this never happens again.
我們已經架好安全告示牌
We've got safety billboards going up,
晚上停止打燈照水塔  還有把護欄建好…
stopped lighting the tower at night,  and we're putting the guardrails in...
這些應該在她衝出道路前  就該做好的
Should've done all that  before she ran off the road.
馬斯特斯先生  你希望我辭職嗎？
Would you like me to resign, Mr. Masters?
只要你說一聲，我就會下台
Just say the word and it's done.
如果這會帶給你慰藉
If it will bring you any satisfaction.
我問過牧師一次
I asked the reverend once,
「我們該怎麼面對  這種失去感覺的痛苦？」
"What are we supposed to do  in the face of so much senseless pain?"
他跟我說
And he said to me,
「我們還能做什麼
"What else can we do
「只能將這沒有意義的事
"but take what seems meaningless,
「轉變成有意義的事？」
"and try to make something  meaningful from it?"
他沒有錯
He's right.
這是上帝透過我們幫助人
That's how God works through us.
你會讓我幫你嗎？
Will you let me work for you?
你必須瞭解我的市民
What you have to understand  about my people
他們都是好人
is that they are a noble people.
謙虛是他們的自豪  這是優點，也是弱點
Humility is their form of pride.  It is their strength. It is their weakness.
只要你能在他們面前  低聲下氣
And ifyou can humble yourself before them,
他們會為你做任何事
they will do anything you ask.
告訴我們獎學金的事
Tell us more about the scholarship.
你好
Hey.
- 你好  - 你在做什麼？
-Hey.  -What're you doing?
- 工作  - 做什麼？
-Working.  -On what?
基地重組與關閉委員會的事  進度有點落後
The BRAC Commission stuff.  I'm behind on it.
今天是週日
It's Sunday.
那又怎樣？
So?
你通常週末不工作
You don't usually work on the weekend.
今天不一樣
Well, now I do.
你想喝咖啡的話，廚房裏有
There's coffee in the kitchen  if you want some.
彼得？
Peter?
彼得
Peter.
如果我決定留下來  是因為這是我要的
If I decide to stay,  it's because it's what I want,
不是因為你
not what you want.
我明白
I understand.
你在看的書面證詞  是哪一個版本？
Which draft are you reading  of the written testimony?
你週四寄來的
The one you sent out on Thursday.
事實上我在週五改了一些  可以給你看嗎？
I actually changed it on Friday.  Can I show you?
我覺得我們可以  先從工作數目開始
Yeah, I was thinking that  we could start with job numbers,
再處理經濟乘數  這樣的順序會比較好
and then go to economic multipliers,  instead of the other way around.
你覺得呢？
What do you think?
看看是什麼情況
Let's see what it looks like.
想像一下，一個17歲女孩  開車以時速90公里
Picture this, a 17-year-old girl  traveling at 60 miles an hour
在沒有其他車子的情況下  打滑撞到護欄
spins out of control in no traffic,  she hits a guardrail,
但如果她有系安全帶  她有系
but if she's wearing a seatbelt,  which she was,
她的車沒有翻轉三次  掉進六公尺的溝渠
and her car doesn't roll over  three times down a 20-foot ditch,
車有掉下去  那這個女孩也許還會活著
which it did,  then that young woman is still alive.
但是你知道嗎？
But you know what?
郡長沒有建這些護欄
The county administrator  didn't build those guardrails,
所以現在她死了
so now she's dead.
我們查了成文法  護欄是屬於郡監督範圍
We looked up the statute.  Guardrails are under county supervision.
你要把矛頭轉到我身上嗎？
Are you trying to turn this around on me?
- 還不只這些，歐倫  - 你的地役權
-That's not all, Oren.  -Your easement.
每隔兩年皮德蒙電力公司
You see every couple of years,  the Piedmont Electric,
都會申請電線通過蓋弗尼
they apply to bring power lines  through Gaffney.
他們的路線剛好經過你的地
The route comes right through your lot.
吉和我一直反對他們  如果今年他們重新申請呢？
Now Gene and I always fight them off,  but this year, if they were to re-apply?
國家徵用權
Eminent domain.
要把這棟美麗的房子拆了  會很可惜
It'd be such a shame to have  to tear down this beautiful home.
去你的，法蘭
Fuck you, Frank.
你不可以到我家  一副你是老大的樣子
You can't just roll up on my property  and act like you own it.
但是我可以
But I can.
我們已經做了
We just did.
我贏了這區11次
I've won this district 11 times.
你覺得我是靠運氣和握手嗎？
Do you think that's just luck  and a firm handshake?
不過讓我跟你說  我不是來報仇的
But I'll tell you what.  I'm not a vindictive person.
如果每個人都可以贏  我不想看到任何人輸
I don't like for anybody to lose  if everybody can win.
所以我會幫你當選第四區席位  你保留房子，我保留第五區
So I'm gonna help you get elected in the 4th.  You get to keep your house. I keep the 5th.
不要再提桃子水塔的事  皆大歡喜，你覺得如何？
We put the Peachoid behind us.  And everybody's happy. What do you say?
好吧，你考慮一下
Well, that's alright. You think about it.
我相信你會做對的事
I'm sure you'll do the right thing.
我期待在國會看到你，歐倫
And I'm looking forward  to having you in Congress, Oren.
有朋友在對邊總是好事
It's always good to have friends  on the other side of the aisle.
《夜線新聞》要挖我過去
I've been offered a spot on Nightline.
你想聽我的意見嗎？
You want my advice?
不只是想，我很需要
I don't want it, I need it.
眼睛閉起來
Close your eyes.
好的
Okay.
現在是11點25分
It's 11:25.
《夜線新聞》要開始了  上百萬的觀眾在收看
Nightline is about to come on.  Millions of people are watching.
你在哪裏？家裏？
Where are you? Home?
不是
No.
- 在攝影棚？  - 對
-At the studio?  -Yes.
你看到什麼？
And what do you see?
我看到燈光跟攝影機
I see lights. I see a camera.
錄影的小紅燈亮起  告訴我你聽到什麼
And that little red dot goes on.  Tell me what you hear.
我聽到我的聲音
I hear my voice.
那些上百萬的觀眾  他們聽到什麼？
And those millions of people,  what do they hear?
我的聲音
My voice.
- 他們看到什麼？  - 我的臉
-And what do they see?  -My face.
所以你不需要我的意見
So you don't need my advice.
翰默史密會瘋掉
Hammerschmidt's gonna freak.
你不想在會被解雇的地方  工作吧，喬伊
You don't want to work anywhere  you're not willing to get fired from, Zoe.
停滯不前對你我來說  就像淹溺一樣
Treading water is the same as drowning  for people like you and me.
- 祝你好運，我會收看  - 等一下
-Good luck. I'll be watching.  -Hey, wait.
- 什麼事？  - 你何時回來？
-Yes?  -When do you get back?
我回來的時候，你會知道
When I get back, you'll know.
- 你好，南茜  - 歡迎你回來，議員
-Hello, Nancy.  -Welcome back, sir.
琳達瓦克斯找過你
Linda Vasquez called for you.
跟她說我幾小時後  會回電報告進展
Tell her I'll call in a couple hours  with an update.
- 好的  - 議員
-Very well.  -Sir,
如果你有任何需要  凱爾會在
unless you need anything,  Kyle has you covered.
不用了，回家吧
No. Go home.
- 你這個週末表現很好  - 謝謝你，議員
-You did well this weekend.  -Thank you, sir.
你回家之前  可以幫我一個忙嗎？
And before you go home,  can you do me a favor?
請你順道到我家  把這些花給克萊兒
Would you swing by my house  and make sure these get to Claire?
好的，議員
Yes, sir.
謝謝你的耐性，議員
And thank you, sir, for being so patient.
好的
Okay.